[
  {
    "pregunta": "Canadá",
    "respuesta": "Ottawa"
  },
  {
    "pregunta": "Estados Unidos",
    "respuesta": "Washington DC"
  },
  {
    "pregunta": "México",
    "respuesta": "México DF"
  },
  {
    "pregunta": "Belice",
    "respuesta": "Belmopán"
  },
  {
    "pregunta": "Costa rica",
    "respuesta": "San José"
  },
  {
    "pregunta": "El Salvador",
    "respuesta": "San Salvador"
  },
  {
    "pregunta": "Guatemala",
    "respuesta": "Ciudad de Guatemala"
  },
  {
    "pregunta": "Honduras",
    "respuesta": "Tegucigalpa"
  },
  {
    "pregunta": "Nicaragua",
    "respuesta": "Managua"
  },
  {
    "pregunta": "Panamá",
    "respuesta": "Panamá"
  },
  {
    "pregunta": "Argentina",
    "respuesta": "Buenos Aires"
  },
  {
    "pregunta": "Bolivia",
    "respuesta": "Sucre"
  },
  {
    "pregunta": "Brasil",
    "respuesta": "Brasilia"
  },
  {
    "pregunta": "Chile",
    "respuesta": "Santiago de Chile"
  },
  {
    "pregunta": "Colombia",
    "respuesta": "Bogotá"
  },
  {
    "pregunta": "Ecuador",
    "respuesta": "Quito"
  },
  {
    "pregunta": "Paraguay",
    "respuesta": "Asunción"
  },
  {
    "pregunta": "Perú",
    "respuesta": "Lima"
  },
  {
    "pregunta": "Surinam",
    "respuesta": "Parabarimo"
  },
  {
    "pregunta": "Trinidad y Tobago",
    "respuesta": "Puerto España"
  },
  {
    "pregunta": "Uruguay",
    "respuesta": "Montevideo"
  },
  {
    "pregunta": "Venezuela",
    "respuesta": "Caracas"
  },
  {
    "pregunta": "Antigua y Barbuda",
    "respuesta": "Saint John"
  },
  {
    "pregunta": "Bahamas",
    "respuesta": "Nasáu"
  },
  {
    "pregunta": "Barbados",
    "respuesta": "Bridgetown"
  },
  {
    "pregunta": "Cuba",
    "respuesta": "La Habana"
  },
  {
    "pregunta": "Dominica",
    "respuesta": "Roseau"
  },
  {
    "pregunta": "Granada",
    "respuesta": "Saint George"
  },
  {
    "pregunta": "Guyana",
    "respuesta": "Georgetown"
  },
  {
    "pregunta": "Haití",
    "respuesta": "Puerto Príncipe"
  },
  {
    "pregunta": "Jamaica",
    "respuesta": "Kingston"
  },
  {
    "pregunta": "República Dominicana",
    "respuesta": "Santo Domingo"
  },
  {
    "pregunta": "San Cristóbal y Nieves",
    "respuesta": "Basseterre"
  },
  {
    "pregunta": "San Vicente y las Granadinas",
    "respuesta": "Kingstown"
  },
  {
    "pregunta": "Santa Lucía",
    "respuesta": "Castries"
  }
]